ANDY CHECO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT



(917) 736-0925



andycheco25@gmail.com



checo-portfolio.herokuapp.com/ 🔗



github.com/savedcity 🔗



in linkedin.com/in/andy-checo 🔗

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, JQuery, React
- Python, DJango
- CSS, Sass, Bootstrap
- HTML
- REST APIs
- Node.js, Express.js
- JWT, Firebase, Bcrypt, **Express Session**
- MongoDB, Mongoose
- SQL, PSQL, SQLite
- · Bash, Git, Github

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Mar 2021 - June 2021 Software Engineer Immerse

NYC College Of Technology

August 2016 - June 2017 Art In Advertisement

PROFILE

I've always been driven by technology and it's potential, and software engineering is a field that pushes me to bring that potential out. With my past experience, multitasking, time management, and great detail work is where I thrive the most. My greatest achievements are the projects I've built which are an image of my abilities, uniqueness and proficiency so I take a lot of honor in them. I am beyond thrilled to be starting in a field where I'll be doing what I love.

PROJECTS

Spamazon 🔗

- An e-commerce app with features like CRUD, authentication, and full cart functionality including a mock purchase.
- Used: React (class comp), Javascript, PSQL, Python, Django, HTML, CSS, and full authentication with Firebase.

Reviewt 🔗

- Created an app with the idea of having users post reviews on their most favorite (or hateful) products.
- Used: Javascript, JQuery, EJS, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, and full authentication with express session and bcrypt.

myHome ∂

- A realtor app where you can find, as well as list, homes in the southern states
- Used: React (functional comp), Javascript, MongoDB, Express, HTML, CSS, and full authentication with JWT and Bcrypt.

More projects on my portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Fellow

General Assembly

3 months | 2021 - 2021

- Learned various software languages, frameworks, libraries and tools.
- Completed projects, tasks, and assignments using skills learned.
- Worked alongside other classmates in order to complete projects and assignments as well as working together with github while communicating accurately.

Remote Customer Service Agent

Various projects including Apple and HBO 2 Years | 2019 - 2021

- Opened and maintained customer accounts by recording account information
- Maintained financial accounts by processing customer adjustments
- Prepared product or service reports by collecting and analyzing customer information
- Meeting personal/team sales targets and call handling quotas